JOSE MARTOS

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, SASS, RWD, JavaScript, ES6, jQuery, Vue.js, React, Typescript, Mocha, Chai, Node.js, Express

Webpack, Gulp, Parcel, Babel, PostCSS, ESlint, Prettier

Page optimization, SEO, JIRA, Git, Docker, Jenkins

COURSES

- React v16.8 (5h | 2019)
- Photoshop & Ilustrator CS5 (160h | 2012)
- Systems and networking (534h | 2006)

TOOLS

- Invision, Zeplin, Avocode, Fireworks, Photoshop
- Sequel Pro, HeidiSQL, PhpMyAdmin, MySQL, Firebird
- WebStorm, Sublime Text, IntelliJ, Aptana

PERSONAL INTERESTS

Trekking, Traveling, Reading, Photography, Martial arts

CONTACT

martosjosele@gmail.com Based in Munich 10.07.1987 – Spain martosjose.com

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Developer with +9 years of experience. Eager for knowledge, creative and fast learner. Considers virtues such as politeness, code quality, punctuality, sense of humour, team work, problem-solving, reliability as well as proactivity vital within the working life. Looking for a suitable position in an already-stablished company, where to share and adquire new ideas, thoughts and abilities.

PROFESSIONAL CAREER

Front-end Developer

Pantaflix GmbH - Berlin (Mar 2017 - Sep 2018)

- Implemented a CMS tool for the customer care department using Vue.js, responsible for the set-up with Webpack and further development
- Responsible for the front-end on a CMS for filmmakers and users, using plain $\mbox{\sf JavaScript}$ and $\mbox{\sf Twig}$
- Implemented new features on the main website, using jQuery and Node.js

Front-end Developer

Team2Venture GmbH - Berlin (Oct 2014 - Feb 2017)

- Participated in a CMS for external companies to handle freelancers and projects, using plain JavaScript and Scala templates
- Responsible for the development of a hybrid mobile app, using AngularJS
- Implemented new features on the main website, participating on a migration from Backbone and RequireJS to plain JavaScript and Browserify + Gulp

Full-stack Developer

Dreamsite - Madrid (Jun 2012 - Sep 2014)

- Developed +15 corporation websites
- Integrated designs in Wordpress pages
- Managed and updated websites, applications and already implemented tools

Junior Full-stack Developer

Uniagro SL - Málaga (Jul 2009 - May 2012)

- Designed and developed +25 corporation websites
- Designed logos and banners
- Managed and updated websites, applications and already implemented tools

EDUCATION

Senior Technician in Computer Applications Development (2007 - 2009) IES Pedro Espinosa, Antequera, Málaga

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native | English: C1 | German: B1